pc-cleaners.com 2012-09-20

# PC Cleaner

This Privacy Statement applies to PC Cleaners Inc. ("PC Cleaners") and its worldwide corporate affiliates ("we", "our" or "us"). This Privacy Statement does not apply to the products or websites of our business partners or to any other third parties, even if their products or websites are linked to or from our website. We recommend you review the privacy statements of the other parties with whom you interact. 

This Privacy Statement governs personal information we collect from our customers and online from our website users ("you"), through our products, services, software, websites, contacts or our relationships with you. 

For the purposes of this Privacy Statement, "corporate affiliates" means any entity or joint venture that is wholly or partially owned or controlled by PC Cleaners Inc... "Business partners" means any subcontractor, vendor or other entity with whom we have an ongoing business relationship to provide products, services, or information. "Personal information" means information which identifies you, such as your name, telephone number, and e-mail address. 

#### **Information We Collect**

**We may ask you to provide personal information when you**

  * Use our website;
  * Use our products;
  * Create a PC Cleaners account;
  * Request services, support, or information;
  * Place orders for products or product subscription activation keys;
  * Participate in surveys, sweepstakes, or other promotional activities;
  * Subscribe to newsletters, promotional e-mails, or other materials; or
  * Contact us.

Information we may request includes your name, e-mail address, home address and telephone number. If you make an order, we may ask for your home address, telephone number. Job applicants may be requested to provide information such as educational background, employment experience and job interest. If you contact us for e-mail technical support, we may ask you for information on which product you are using, which version of Windows you are using, the nature of your issue, and any other information pertinent to the support request. If you use our products, in addition to your name and e-mail address, we will also receive technical information regarding your computer specifications. We may also collect your business or company information, title or department and other information (including demographic information). Any forms that you may fill in will indicate whether information requested is mandatory or voluntary. 

You can browse the PC Cleaners website without creating an account, but you may need to create an account when you purchase something. When you create an account at PC Cleaners.com, you can choose to save your billing and shipping information in the "My Account / View or Modify My Account Information" section of the PC Cleaners website. You may log in to your account to change or delete this saved information anytime.

We may collect information about your visits to our websites, including the pages you view, the links you click, search terms you enter and other actions you take in connection with the PC Cleaners websites and services. We may also collect certain information from the browser you used to come to our website, such as your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type and language, access times, the Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") of the website that referred you to our website and to which URL you browse away from our site if you click on a link on our site.

In order to offer you a more consistent and personalized experience in your interactions with PC Cleaners, information collected through one source may be combined with information obtained through other PC Cleaners resources. We may also supplement the information we collect with information obtained from other parties as well.

Some PC Cleaners services or products may be co-branded and offered in conjunction with another company. If you register for or use such services or products, both PC Cleaners and the other company may receive information collected in conjunction with the co-branded services or products, and may use the information according to each company's privacy statement and other agreements with you.

#### How We Use Your Personal Information

**PC Cleaners uses your personal and technical information to:**

  * Deliver the services and support, or carry out the transactions you have requested. 
  * Send communications to you, such as your transactions status (for example, order confirmations), information about products and services available from PC Cleaners and its corporate affiliates, promotional offers, newsletters, and surveys.
  * Customize, analyze, and improve our products, services (including our website), technologies, communications and relationship with you.
  * Enforce our conditions of sale, website terms and/or separate contracts (if applicable) with you.
  * Prevent fraud and other prohibited or illegal activities.

Personal information collected may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which PC Cleaners or its corporate affiliates, subsidiaries, agents or service providers maintain facilities, and by using PC Cleaners products and services, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. 

#### **Disclosing Personal Information**

We will never share your information with third parties.

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy products, subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing privacy policy (unless, of course, you consent otherwise). Also, in the event that PC Cleaners, or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.

#### **How We Secure Your Personal Information**

PC Cleaners is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure, such as encryption, passwords, physical security, etc. While we strive to protect your personal information, PC Cleaners cannot ensure or warrant that the personal information or private communications you transmit to us will always remain private, and you do so at your own risk.

If a password is used to help protect your accounts and personal information, it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not share this information with anyone. If you are sharing a computer with anyone you should always log out before leaving a site or service to protect access to your information from subsequent users.

If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from United States law, including those whose privacy laws may be more strict than United States law, please note that you are transferring your personal information to the United States to PC Cleaners, where it will be stored. By providing your personal information you consent to such transfer and storage of personal information in the United States (or any other region outside the European Union where such personal information may be stored). PC Cleaners will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

#### **Collection and Use of Children's Personal Information**

PC Cleaners takes children's privacy seriously. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 through our websites.

If you are under 18 years of age, please do not submit any personal information through our websites without the express consent and participation of a parent or guardian.

#### **How We Use Cookies**

PC Cleaners websites use "cookies" to enable you to sign in to our services and to help personalize your online experience. We use cookies to store your preferences and other information on your computer in order to save you time by eliminating the need to repeatedly enter the same information and to display your personalized content and appropriate advertising on your later visits to these websites.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of PC Cleaners websites and services that depend on cookies.

#### **Third-Party Websites and Services**

Please note we do not give out our members information to third parties.

Please be aware that, in providing services on PC Cleaners's behalf, our business partners may collect personal information about you.=

#### **Changes to Our Global Privacy Statement Regarding Customer and Online User Information**

We will occasionally update this Privacy Statement. When we post changes to this Privacy Statement, we will revise the Effective Date at the end of this paragraph. If there are material changes to this Privacy Statement or in how PC Cleaners will use your personal information, we will notify you by prominently posting a notice of such changes prior to implementing the change. We encourage you to periodically review this statement to be informed of how PC Cleaners is protecting your personal information.

Effective Date: January 1, 2009.

#### Contacting Us

If you would like to contact us for any reason regarding our privacy practices, please write us at the following address:

PC Cleaners Inc.  
Attention: Privacy Policy  
220 Newport Center Dr. Suite 197  
Newport Beach, CA 92660
